[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 8, "question": "Did he do that to you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "do", "that", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 9, "answer": "You'll have to ask him.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'ll", "have", "to", "ask", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 10, "question": "Why are you reluctant to say?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "reluctant", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 11, "answer": "Because we have a show we're doing and it just -- I just don't want to say any incriminating things that are going to make it harder to kind of make peace and have it appealing.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "we", "have", "a", "show", "we", "'re", "doing", "and", "it", "just", "--", "I", "just", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "say", "any", "incriminating", "things", "that", "are", "going", "to", "make", "it", "harder", "to", "kind", "of", "make", "peace", "and", "have", "it", "appealing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Do you ever watch it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "watch", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "When was the last time?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "the", "last", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Last night.", "answer_tokens": ["Last", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "I could have had you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "could", "have", "had", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "She's aged a lot better.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "aged", "a", "lot", "better", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "When you look back, if you were your own biggest critic here, what would you say you were like as a father?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "back", ",", "if", "you", "were", "your", "own", "biggest", "critic", "here", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "you", "were", "like", "as", "a", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Great.", "answer_tokens": ["Great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "Do you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "When you look back on what happened, when did you start to see things just go wrong, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "back", "on", "what", "happened", ",", "when", "did", "you", "start", "to", "see", "things", "just", "go", "wrong", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "WP", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Tatum and I were enormously close.", "answer_tokens": ["Tatum", "and", "I", "were", "enormously", "close", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "You probably thought, too bad for him but pretty good for me, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "probably", "thought", ",", "too", "bad", "for", "him", "but", "pretty", "good", "for", "me", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "Not really.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "And she was the love of your life?", "question_tokens": ["And", "she", "was", "the", "love", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "What would you do differently?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "do", "differently", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "Well, I was getting pulled.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "getting", "pulled", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "If you had your time again, what would you do differently to try and resolve it?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "had", "your", "time", "again", ",", "what", "would", "you", "do", "differently", "to", "try", "and", "resolve", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "I would have done something differently because I hate how it went.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "have", "done", "something", "differently", "because", "I", "hate", "how", "it", "went", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "But she never did?", "question_tokens": ["But", "she", "never", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "Never did.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Do you really believe that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "really", "believe", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "I think it's highly possible.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "highly", "possible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "Because one felt very neglected and left out.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "one", "felt", "very", "neglected", "and", "left", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Farrah"]}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "UH", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "How did you feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "It was OK, except Farrah said she blames you.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "OK", ",", "except", "Farrah", "said", "she", "blames", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "Did you ever say sorry to Tatum?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "say", "sorry", "to", "Tatum", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "Many times.", "answer_tokens": ["Many", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tatum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "How did that make you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "that", "make", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "It was horrible.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "horrible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Do you believe that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "I know of one.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "of", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Do you still think that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "think", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "Uh-huh.", "answer_tokens": ["Uh-huh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "When was that?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "That was several weeks before the funeral.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "several", "weeks", "before", "the", "funeral", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "How do I look?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "I", "look", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Not good.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "Tatum is?", "question_tokens": ["Tatum", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Farrah"]}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "How are you coping without Farrah?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "coping", "without", "Farrah", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "You know, Farrah was a very strong presence in my life.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "Farrah", "was", "a", "very", "strong", "presence", "in", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "What can you say to him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "you", "say", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "I say to him that's not what she wants.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "say", "to", "him", "that", "'s", "not", "what", "she", "wants", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "Do you like movies?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "movies", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "I don't go very often.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "go", "very", "often", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "Do you have one in you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "one", "in", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 646, "question": "Why not?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 647, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "``", "WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 653, "question": "After \"Love Story\" became this huge, global hit?", "question_tokens": ["After", "``", "Love", "Story", "''", "became", "this", "huge", ",", "global", "hit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 654, "answer": "Look, I did \"What's Up Doc\" and that was a huge success.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "did", "``", "What", "'s", "Up", "Doc", "''", "and", "that", "was", "a", "huge", "success", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "Do you think you have a temper?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "have", "a", "temper", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "Yes, sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "How much of that do you blame yourself for?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "that", "do", "you", "blame", "yourself", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "Well, we have the genetic makeup.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "have", "the", "genetic", "makeup", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "Do you have any relationship with him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "relationship", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "He is your flesh and blood?", "question_tokens": ["He", "is", "your", "flesh", "and", "blood", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "I don't know, I'm going to get DNA.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "get", "DNA", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 724, "question": "Did you go to the hospital after that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "go", "to", "the", "hospital", "after", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 725, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 729, "question": "You didn't go?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "n't", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 730, "answer": "No, I had the limo pick them up, because that could be much faster.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "had", "the", "limo", "pick", "them", "up", ",", "because", "that", "could", "be", "much", "faster", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 738, "question": "It is true?", "question_tokens": ["It", "is", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 739, "answer": "Not around them.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "around", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 747, "question": "Did he do that to you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "do", "that", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 748, "answer": "You'll have to ask him.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'ll", "have", "to", "ask", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 749, "question": "Why are you reluctant to say?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "reluctant", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 750, "answer": "Because we have a show we're doing and I don't want to say incriminating that are going to make it harder to kind of make peace and have a healing.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "we", "have", "a", "show", "we", "'re", "doing", "and", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "say", "incriminating", "that", "are", "going", "to", "make", "it", "harder", "to", "kind", "of", "make", "peace", "and", "have", "a", "healing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 769, "question": "Doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 770, "answer": "It doesn't hurt, no.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "n't", "hurt", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 771, "question": "Can it?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 772, "answer": "She had a career.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "had", "a", "career", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 778, "question": "OK?", "question_tokens": ["OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 779, "answer": "You said this before we watched the clip, though, that there were drugs around when they were young.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "said", "this", "before", "we", "watched", "the", "clip", ",", "though", ",", "that", "there", "were", "drugs", "around", "when", "they", "were", "young", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 786, "question": "Could they have been taking them without you know something?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "they", "have", "been", "taking", "them", "without", "you", "know", "something", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 787, "answer": "They could have been taking it, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "could", "have", "been", "taking", "it", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 793, "question": "But you did give them to Griffin?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "did", "give", "them", "to", "Griffin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 794, "answer": "No, no, but he had access.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "but", "he", "had", "access", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Griffin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 805, "question": "'NEAL: Oh, the future?", "question_tokens": ["'NEAL", ":", "Oh", ",", "the", "future", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 806, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 809, "question": "Do you feel positive about it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "positive", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 810, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 817, "question": "You think you can?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "you", "can", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 818, "answer": "Uh-huh, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Uh-huh", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ":", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 832, "question": "How would you like to be remembered?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "like", "to", "be", "remembered", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 833, "answer": "It was a childhood -- children and a man to men.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "childhood", "--", "children", "and", "a", "man", "to", "men", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]